[Music]
so
so gorgeous
[Music]
it is so quiet here
you'll probably be able to hear my dog
throughout this entire thing but besides
him and all his noises um
it is so quiet and lovely right now
the sun is peeking through the trees and
it's
shining light through the petals of the
spring beauties
on the side of the cliff and it's
it's just stunning
is just my favorite time of year for
sure
and it's funny because for me
spring is a very
sacred time for lack of a better word
um
it's always a very special time it's
it's always the time where i find myself
feeling the most energetic and the most
joyous
and it's been interesting to come to
this season that is such a special
season for me
and find myself not feeling well
and that's been a interesting wake-up
call so
it inspired me to sit down and kind of
make a
unplanned video and connect with you and
ask you how you're doing and if you're
taking care of yourself
for me
several months ago once we realized we
were going to thanks to the kindness of
luke's
parents
purchase a home next to them i decided
to extend my work hours because i knew
it would be
extremely helpful
i was just
constantly in that mindset of preparing
for this change
for me last week was a really profound
experience because
i made
a video
i filmed a lot of that video in this
forest
and there was this moment while i was
filming where i was just
standing
next to a tree without shoes on just
barefoot and
staring up at the branches just finding
trying to
decide what i had in mind for the video
and i realized i am
so happy right now and i've not spent
that much time in the forest
and then i also realized it kind of hit
me like a wave of how bone tired
i was
from the last few months
how i just felt like
constantly working
was allowing so much that i wanted to
happen
but the flip side is that you do hit
this wall i found that my anxiety was
getting a lot worse and that i was
waking up at night with just kind of
palpitations in my chest and and
this feeling of numbness through all my
limbs
and
having a really hard time sleeping
because everything felt so tingly and
numb and it was a very strange and
rather frightening experience
and
will i be able to
provide for the people i love
will i be able to have people rely on me
and not fail them when i made last
week's video
i loved every moment of making that
video and
that leads me to what i wanted to say
which was thank you
because
no matter how i'm feeling
filming videos being outdoors
or being indoors baking or doing crafts
or
doing anything that i'm able to edit and
put together in artistic ways brings me
so much joy and peace in my life and and
to spend more time outdoors
to spend more time connecting
with the trees and with the earth and
with my spirit and
prayer and
there is still parts of my life where
i'm letting fear dictate my actions i
think i need to take a little bit of
time to
work on that if you feel so inclined if
you could share your words of wisdom in
the comments section
a community of so many lovely people
has so much more wisdom and so much life
experiences and so much
beauty to offer
each other than i could ever offer to
you
and
how you find peace in your daily life
when you truly don't have time when you
don't really have options when you have
responsibilities or people relying on
you if you don't have any option but to
work as hard as you've been working you
know how do you rejuvenate in the midst
of all that that's how i've been feeling
recently i've been feeling all these a
lot of weight of responsibility a lot
that i just put on myself offering
love and support to all of you and i
think it is so important for all of us
to ask for help if we need it
yeah so i'm going to try to take some
time to
work on
my breathing and and feeling calm
because all this
numbness and palpitations and kind of
panicky moments um
yeah really aren't good for me and take
some time
to
breathe
and
finish up all the paperwork for this
house and finally move in
permanently
it's all getting ready for a new
beginning
and
it's happening and
i am sending you all my love
and i will see you very soon take care
goodbye
you